

## **UI/UX Developer**

PHONE +60 1123373600

EMAIL work.nazreenhanim@gmail.com

PORTFOLIO findhanim.gitlab.io/home

## Blending artistic vision with innovative solution

It has been 4 years since I started delivering my skill set and versatile services professionally. Along these journey, collaborating with various teams and projects has shaped my approach and broadened my perspective. These days, I focused on building design systems which combine technical needs with artistic vision that improve development process and user experience. I believe in merging creativity with functionality to deliver the best solutions.

SKILLS TOOLS AND TECHNOLOGIES

UI/UX + Prototyping Figma, Adobe XD, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator

Design System NativeBase, Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS

Front End Development React Native, Gatsby JS, Angular, JavaScript, HTML, CSS

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Platform Development Specialist @ CelcomDigi

January 2023 - Present

Introduced technical design system for B2C and on-going projects, with hands-on contribution to the ideation and front-end development. Also actively collaborate with the developers and UI/UX team.

- Leading the implementation of design system configured from NativeBase for **Next-Gen Consumer** application, which significantly speed up the UI and component development process.
- Introduced Bootstrap to developers for a more comprehensive UI revamp, transitioning from their previous use of Webflow for **CelcomDigi support** website.
- Contributed to the end-to-end process for **Pryce**, starting from initial UI/UX ideation, prototype testing to project development.

### **HIPA (DRIVE) Developer @ Celcom**

January 2021 - December 2022

Involved with the end-to-end process for multiple B2C and internal projects, starting from UI/UX exploration, front-end development and on-going maintenance to ensure seamless integration and alignment throughout the projects' lifecycle.

- Responsible for the UI development of **Pulse** while actively collaborating with both product designers and developers in assisting UI related ad-hoc tasks and issues.
- Mainly involved with the ideation of UI/UX design process that translate into a working prototype for Onboardme
  and We@Celcom. Contributed to the grooming session, development and maintenance of major sprints.
- Involved in the full lifecycle for **Prisma** production, beginning with UI/UX ideation and prototype development, conducting user experience research, extending through project development and maintenance.

### Web and Graphic Designer @ MNC Wireless

December 2019 - January 2021

Contributed to the UI/UX design and digital branding for clients and subsidiary companies. Also hands-on in Wordpress UI development and CMS utilization.

- Responsible for interface design exploration, crafting digital designs tailored to clients' needs, capturing and displaying their identities through visual representation.
- Creating visuals which include branding, seasonal greeting and minor animation for both internal and subsidiary companies.

# **Internship Trainee @ PETRONAS**

February 2019 - July 2019

Played a role in multimedia design and presentation for internal campaigns, while actively collaborated in event management, and assisted in deck preparation.

#### **EDUCATION BACKGROUND**

## **Bachelor of Computer Science (Hons.) Multimedia Computing**

UiTM (2016 - 2019)

### **Diploma of Computer Science**

UiTM (2014 - 2016)

#### **OTHER INTERESTS**

Artistic Passionate about abstract graphic design and coding on Codepen

Cinematography Getting eclectic inspiration from Wes Anderson movies and the Potterworld

Casual Gaming Enjoy building virtual world on Animal Crossing and The Sims

#### **REFERENCES**

Sabri Maslan sabri.maslan@celcomdigi.com

+60 132773880

Carolyn Chen carolyn.chen@mnc.com.my

+60 166916776